

Elsa Lila

O Home: Zografou, 15772, Athens, Greece

Email: <u>elsalila7@gmail.com</u> **\ Phone:** (+30) 6947767783

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/elsa-lila-0667a4162/

Date of birth: 15/09/1997 Nationality: Albanian

ABOUT ME

Enthusiastic focused and motivated Intermediate Developer with almost three years of experience. Ability to apply theoretical concepts in the practical world. Excellent English communication skills- both oral and written. Flexible and adaptable to demands of changing work environments. Team player and also independently responsible.

WORK EXPERIENCE

[08/2023 – Current] Web developer

Self Employed

City: Athens

Country: Greece

This is a personal project for a shop (BlackBerry)

To develop this project are being used:

- Laravel
- MySQL
- HTML5
- CSS

[05/2022 - 11/2022] **Web developer**

Gridcoding

City: Tirana Country: Albania

Business or sector: Information and communication

- Backend developer Laravel
- MySql
- Building and developing databases
- Knowledge of UNIX, Nginx, cPanel

[05/2020 - 05/2022] **Web developer**

Digit Sapiens

City: Tirana

Country: Albania

Business or sector: Information and communication

- · Backend developer Laravel, Javascript, Node.js, PHP
- Frontend developer Angular, Vue.js
- MvSal
- Building and developing databases
- Familiar with Phaser 3 framework
- Familiar with TypeOrm framework
- · Familiar with Trello, Teams, Jira

[02/2020 - 05/2020] **Web developer**

Personal project

City: Tirana Country: Albania

Business or sector: Information and communication

- Accomplished by using PHP language, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, phpMyAdmin
- Buy the necessary equipment for the gym
- Contains five user interfaces (Login, Sign up, Shopping Cart, Checkout, Products), admin page
- Admin can delete, update and save products
- User has the right to view product details, when the user clicks the AddToCart button if the user is not logged in he will be redirect to the Login page, if the user has no account it will be redirected to Sign up page. Also when user clicks the ShoppingCart and Checkout page the user must be initially logged in the system

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[09/2019 - Current]

Scientific Master Information Technology

Faculty of Natural Science

Address: 1001, Tirana, Albania

Field(s) of study: Information and Communication Technologies

- Linux Administration
- Information Systems Analysis
- Cloud computing technologies
- Applied user interface

[09/2016 - 10/2019]

Bachelor Information Technology and Communication

Faculty of Natural Science

Field(s) of study: Information and Communication Technologies

- · Programming and data structure
- Logical systems
- Object oriented programming
- Telecommunication and networks
- System administration and security
- System administration and security
- Knowledge of asp.Net,C#,Javascript,SQL Server,HTML,Css,XML,XSLT

[11/2019 - 03/2020]

Programmer

Tirana Oficce Hub

Address: 1001, Tirana, Albania

Field(s) of study: Information and Communication Technologies

- Combining bootstrap template with HTML5/CSS
- Knowledge of PHP language
- Creating files with PHP, HTML5. CSS, Bootstrap templates
- · Knowledge about phpMyAdmin (creating database,tables, filling tables with data via php language)
- · How to save the works on Bitbucket via Git bash

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Albanian

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1

Italian

LISTENING B1 READING A2 WRITING A2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION A2 SPOKEN INTERACTION A2

Spanish

LISTENING B2 READING A2 WRITING A1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION A2 SPOKEN INTERACTION A2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

PROJECTS

[05/2022 - 11/2022] **Medical Desk**

- Application that allows you to make reservations for health services.
- https://medicaldesk.it/en/home-en/

[01/2022 - 05/2022] CargoFlags

- Backend Nest.js
- Frontend Angular
- · cargoflags.com

[11/2020 - 02/2022] **PECB**

- Backend Laravel
- Frontend Vue.js
- Using HTML, CSS
- pecb.com

[06/2020 - 12/2020] My vehicle

- Backend Node.js
- TypeOrm framework
- Converted from desctop application to web

[05/2020 - 07/2020] **Psychological game**

- Backend Javascript
- Frontend Phaser 3 framework
- Description: tested persons who will testify in a trial, are tested to see if they are capable of testifying and if they fail to pass the levels then their testimony will not be considered

COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Public Speaking

Speaking in public fluently

Strategic Thinking

• Thinking strategically to solve problems

Self-management

Manages the situation independently

Teamwork

• Work in groups and exchange ideas

VOLUNTEERING

[12/2018 - Current] Member of EESTEC LC Tirana

• Member of a non-profit organization called EESTEC LC Tirana, in which we are committed to bringing and sending students abroad.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Tools & Technologies

- Laravel
- Angular
- Javascript
- Vue.js
- MySql
- HTML5
- UNIX
- Nginx
- cPanel
- GitHub
- GitLab